<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aws on Vandy Liu</title>
    <link>https://vandyliu.com/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in aws on Vandy Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vandyliu.com/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Soccer Pick Up Game Bot</title>
      <link>https://vandyliu.com/proj/whatsapp-soccer-pick-up-game-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vandyliu.com/proj/whatsapp-soccer-pick-up-game-bot/</guid>
      <description>The gist of this project came from the fact that I missed the registration time to be a committed member for Thursday indoor soccer games. There are 15 spots, first reserved for committed members and then if they are not all filled, some drop in players are selected to join. To become selected for drop-in, you have to respond to a specific text message that the organizer sends out the day before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Out Alexa Skill (Hackathon)</title>
      <link>https://vandyliu.com/proj/check-out-alexa-skill-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vandyliu.com/proj/check-out-alexa-skill-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Alexa   Languages/Technologies: Node.js, AWS Lambda, MongoDB
An Alexa skill designed to make keeping track of attedance for after-school programs easier. Parents can quickly check their child out with their voice. The supervisors can also see who is still here and who has left with a web UI designed with React. The application was made to help a Boys and Kids club in the Seattle area. We used a MongoDB database and AWS Lambda to run our Alexa skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer games and Python</title>
      <link>https://vandyliu.com/p/soccer-games-and-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vandyliu.com/p/soccer-games-and-python/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been playing soccer for the past 15 years of my life. I love everything about the game and I enjoy playing it a ton. After high school ended, there wasn’t much opportunity for me to play and I got caught up in a lot of other things like school and work. However, I started dropping in at this indoor soccer event every Thursday. Because I missed the registration date, I am not a registered player and can only play if there aren’t enough registered players willing to play that day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
